even the bankrupt lokator and see how the coral
甚至破产的lokator，看看珊瑚如何
outside the smallest things like the behavior about nanoink co-worker
最小的事情之外，例如有关nanoink同事的行为
jorine meeting or the person who caught them a traffic for my own
见面会或为我自己吸引流量的人
experience it very easy to get long at a miner event in your every
在每个矿工中经历很长的时间很容易
day is at 6 how attestation i become anxiously about the future and endless louis my
一天是6点，我如何对未来的焦虑和无休止的路易斯
eat outpost which form cosmac point of view
吃前哨所形成的宇宙观
chapter 9 can enforce with whom and vests somogyi emotional energy and
第9章可以强制与谁并赋予somogyi情绪能量和
really in this video how would like to present you stole i
真的在这部影片中，如何向您介绍我
exercise that could give the mind all the view of the wolf
可以让头脑全神贯注于狼的运动
[Music]
[音乐]
even though practicing stories and can be considered a very serious undertaking
即使练习故事，也可以认为是一项非常认真的工作
there is also a sense of lucy's to find in the words of marcus aurelius
在marcus aurelius的话中也找到了露西的感觉
politics or that in significance so many life's in relation to the bigger picture
政治或意义如此之大的生命与大局有关
a quote the earth will suitcase is already and then be transformed into here en der tool
引述地球将已经手提箱的报价，然后将其转换为此处en der工具
change at infi so far and that is old infini to think about them the us of
到目前为止infi发生了变化，这是古老的infini来考虑他们的
change and alteration endlessly breaking ncl brief mortality
变化和变化无休止地打破ncl短暂死亡率
for becoming there is a quote in the journal cycles of life and death
成为生死日记中的一句名言
creation and recreation how your archives take a grain of sand in the lesson
创作和娱乐您的档案在课程中如何发挥作用
sahara desert camp matter what how in the universe
撒哈拉沙漠营地如何在宇宙中生存
this doesn't take ow that the you experience is intense and reviews or
这并不需要因为您的经历很激烈，并且评论或
constantly single jersey short life span all time i blue planet some time to get
持续不断的单球衣短寿命我一直在蓝色星球上寻找时间
so in t holt in human drama with whom experience emotional disturbances
因此，在经历情感障碍的人类戏剧中，
like anger and ding siety some people are processed with bells and fem willing
像愤怒和叮叮当当一样，有些人会受到钟声和女性的欢迎
to migrate sacrifice is to get to the trap while most likely
迁移牺牲是最有可能进入陷阱
there you snuck for god and 100 years from now
在那里，你为上帝而神，从现在起100年
and they find view belong to the lucky few who is names will be preserved for
他们发现视图属于幸运的少数人，他们的名字将被保留下来
out the centuries it is quiet in significant wmo-loket from a wider
几个世纪以来，它在更广泛的WMO营销中无声无息
perspective considering the and tropic nature of the
角度考虑
universe the earth will disappear wounds your food and destroy it or even and the
宇宙地球消失会伤害您的食物，甚至毁坏它，并且
planet escapes the destruction by a medior
行星逃脱了毁灭性的毁灭
it will eventually be swallowed by the sun we just enters the red giant face
它最终将被我们刚刚进入红色巨人脸的太阳吞噬
who cares den ham much money you have your savings account
谁在乎den ham多少钱，您有您的储蓄帐户
how did the nobel prize just win the bloody wars how guys having great staff will
诺贝尔奖是如何赢得血腥战争的？
Could be insignificant ipods and er or i tired of the chorus
可能是微不足道的ipod和/或我厌倦了合唱
twitter appointed times their destined to be born to grow and to be destroyed
推特任命他们注定要成长并被摧毁的时代
the starrs what you see movie about was and the simoni in movable yard
看电影时看到的星星是和动院子里的simoni
the which winding and then which she has set will be consumed
哪个绕组然后她设定的绕组将被消耗
and how much cease to exist and close the idea about insignificance [ __ ] left some
和多少停止存在，并关闭有关微不足道的猫的想法留下了一些
people to despair what this can also be a very king falls the day-to-day problem
人们感到绝望这也可能是一个非常大的问题
that costs so mini-witch the constant 'striving for goals that how
花费那么多小巫婆不断追求目标，
die marley important about analyzing the past and future abscesses thinking about
马利逝世对于分析过去和未来脓肿的思考很重要
what should be and shoot view all this for me
应该是什么，然后为我查看所有这些
distance and to use it to what really is a more that one of the countless galaxies
距离并将其用于更多的星系之一
in universe what foundation will be left for very great and scarier
在宇宙中，什么基础将留下来，使伟大而可怕
the most modern also soft real time you think about you manage place in the
您想到的最现代，最柔和的实时管理位置
cosmos and toe and exercise colt the view of about this exercise uses a temporary
宇宙和脚趾和练习柯尔特关于这个练习的观点是暂时的
break from my daily care and puts them in a delight
中断我的日常护理，让他们感到高兴
change in a position to wars external links change the way we think about them
改变战争立场外部联系改变了我们对他们的看法
which in turn changes homophile is the story form or meditation allowed the mind
这反过来改变了同性是故事的形式或冥想所允许的思想
you start the view from above my visualizing yourself or vimeo kloos en
您从我的可视化自己或vimeo kloos的上方开始查看
direct environment is like your being watched, the lens asked about the best
直接的环境就像您在观看，镜头询问最佳
telescope pets place fountains of light shows ow
望远镜宠物放光明喷泉ow
no with you and aliens aviation that is able to surf turf
您和外星人航空不可以冲浪
in real time looking at you sitting on a chair or lying in bed in your room
实时看着您坐在椅子上或躺在房间的床上
well de telescope soens auto little and focuses on your hopes and your
好望远镜能使自动对焦少一点，并专注于您的希望和您的
neighborhood you're already quite small and
邻居，你已经很小了，
comparison to all the streets and other houses
与所有街道和其他房屋相比
now it looks at the city and its environment seahawks marjo where it s be
现在它看起来在城市及其环境中
calm and possible to observe you
冷静，有可能观察到你
countries or oceans that charante city rsb could be nothing more
夏朗市rsb可能仅此而已的国家或海洋
than a small that the contents of spread around I walk
比我走走的内容散布的小
watch free dormant legal 6 of potions dat housefeesten areas that who haven't
观看免费休眠的法律6的药水dad housefeesten地区，谁还没有
discovered get worse is to compare your small planet to the
发现变得更糟的是将您的小行星与
other planets spot neptune of you better watch and their turn up tiny compared to
其他行星会更好地监视你的海王星，与它们相比，它们的上升幅度很小
the sun the sun is a giulia big star compare to
太阳太阳是朱利亚的大明星
let c antares hats 115 times its size
让帽子的大小扩大到原来的115倍
above the sam and antares a part of the milky way which contains between
在山姆上方，并注视着银河系的一部分，其中包含
towel fifty and up to 150 trillion stars when in stern the telescope away from
in着望远镜，使它远离远处时，可以擦拭五十到一百五十万亿颗恒星
a galaxy and the instant cold it gets ridgid millions
一个银河系，瞬间变冷，成千上万的ridgid
even billions of al door galaxy's many even bigger than our own
甚至数十亿个门星系甚至比我们自己的星系还要大
meditating up smolia in the grants cream or frank's
在奶油或弗兰克的赠款中冥想斯莫莉亚
push ortho realizar north wcs important matters the les amies tank is angry
推正交重要事项les amies坦克生气
flow and action thank you for watching
流程和行动感谢您的观看
[Music]
[音乐]